{ "backgroundcolor":"#000000",
 "height":58,
 "layers":[
        {
         "compression":"zlib",
         "data":"eJztm0FuwkAMRbPrgbh9l+1pskPqBSqkRkpHJBkHZ\/xt3uJtSkQ+9n9RgDJP0zQDwGXcD7jqHO3j0XPonUumuVt2ENGtHjzPr5r\/zPN+DdjfEUuG6FkcncPzeI+uevTq6rlYXlfE68nqS\/Qc4Hoye7KALzCSHlc+hFHxJXoO4NenXl+ePf4lTrQra2egDke+7LkS3cWtbkbnIFdN9pxZjmn\/fhOe8\/cf0Tmy5FLc409DdJ5n83rmzHIMvtTNpbjHDL48HOh9\/4IvdXIp7jGjL+1x+FIzl+Ie8WUcqr1UzaW4xwq+zBO+VMyluEd8GYdqL1VzKe4xoy9792T4UieX4h7xZRyqvVTNpbjHCr7wfr9mLsU94ss4VHupmktxj9l92ft+\/ybwGhY+G6LzkOscqr60vc\/uyyPPch1XumaSywa+vPf+yWUjoy\/r4\/CFXCPBl\/feP7ls4Mt7759cNrL50h639\/tKJV\/a31tH5yHXOVR9edDjyzztOwM1iO5iVl8sztwgNYr3CVV82XIGcrL2JbqHVX3BmTrgi5YvSp5ZZhLdY3zJ50tPx0b3cvRsovuML7V8gXHdviIHvtjBFx8iHHk1B77YwRd\/Ijw5kwFf7OBLXfDFH3ypDb74gi+1wRdf8KU2+OILvtTF8v6F\/x87pp0XvtQCX3zBl7pYP0\/Gl2P2fInOBq+BL\/7gS13wxZ8tX6Jzwevgiz\/4UpceX+6Tpi+qrH3hXqweVmegDz4Xq0uvM1u\/74f\/PJtd9I4hzhuwEb1XwJtMRO8TcMa7w7gCnkT3O6q3uAIjuuP5XApdVcgA+VC8jkd0NPr8kIsre6LsCYAieAJgB0cA3ptfIyiJ5w==",
         "encoding":"base64",
         "height":58,
         "name":"back",
         "opacity":0.5,
         "type":"tilelayer",
         "visible":true,
         "width":204,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "compression":"zlib",
         "data":"eJzt3EluwzAMQFHueqBcMOfKMifqEVIvAhhqLIk2JVLMfwBXHcy4+kXTSQTASL+NGXWN8uXRjLwftfdvfZ3a9UZrPcaesbz+1bcftf+Z9\/s88XisbTtEuBeta1i+vsVZtThXo++L5nF5PJ5v6IVZc45476UZemFmTunTedzmJ+hE6cX7PjB256n2+W\/vqJXIE4X3fWDsp9ZLrZVo2Esn6l5R1Zp5o5fr2CuHM73cJO59Zi+dqHtF9b5fWwO9z1\/oRY+9cjjqpUQv17BXDvQyB3vl0NuLCL1cwV450Msc7JVD7\/N9EXq5gr1yoJc52CsHvp88B3vlQC9zsFcOPb3Ufr5\/m7lsw0Pkvh\/vfd4exUQRda+oynO\/ei\/ASPQC9Kv1skcvAL0AGmd7eQq94Psc9VJapZfy762jYK88enoRqTfD5Bi0fepF28yNWXYifp0QmaYXkf\/NMOvOvhf00fYi4vOxZeglgpG9nH27EaPhfY7pJa6jXnrO2OxzOZv3eaaXeK70gnlne8Qe9KJHLzY8Grm6B73o0Ys9j07O7EAvevSSF73Yo5fc6MUWveRGL7boJTd6sUUveWmev\/D7Y23l\/aKXXOjFFr3kpf1+Mr201XrB2ujFHr3kRS\/2jnrB+np62f9tJb207XvZhl7yoBd79JKbthmmf\/7u3Z1e8tE04\/2\/BKJP0Qq9JNbTDaMf5OZ9vrIN8vM+Y7PPMK3Akvf59jq3tIKzLM9K1D4s9wUifh73OKPe18daRp6TyJ0AEdEJoEcjwHd7Ac5qgpo=",
         "encoding":"base64",
         "height":58,
         "name":"front",
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"tilelayer",
         "visible":true,
         "width":204,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#5555ff",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"mods",
         "objects":[
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":712,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedrustypanel",
                     "front":"slopedrustypanel"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":376,
                 "y":48
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":713,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":256,
                 "x":384,
                 "y":40
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":714,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"castlewalls1",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":376,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":735,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":1560,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":758,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":72,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":760,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"castlewalls1",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":576,
                 "x":984,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":779,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":376,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":780,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"castlewalls1",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":72,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":784,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":64,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":786,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":368,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":40,
                 "id":787,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedscrappanel",
                     "colorVariant":"6"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "colorVariant":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":16,
                 "x":352,
                 "y":160
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":788,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "colorVariant":"7",
                     "front":"ledgebrick"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "colorVariant":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":32,
                 "x":344,
                 "y":152
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":789,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":344,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":112,
                 "id":792,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":1560,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":793,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":576,
                 "x":984,
                 "y":360
                }, 
                {
                 "height":88,
                 "id":794,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":976,
                 "y":224
                }, 
                {
                 "height":296,
                 "id":795,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedrustypanel"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":1280,
                 "y":64
                }, 
                {
                 "height":296,
                 "id":796,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedrustypanel"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":1256,
                 "y":64
                }, 
                {
                 "height":296,
                 "id":797,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedscrappanel",
                     "colorVariant":"6"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "colorVariant":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":16,
                 "x":1264,
                 "y":64
                }, 
                {
                 "height":40,
                 "id":805,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedscrappanel",
                     "colorVariant":"6"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "colorVariant":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":16,
                 "x":960,
                 "y":160
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":806,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":952,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":807,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "colorVariant":"7",
                     "front":"ledgebrick"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "colorVariant":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":32,
                 "x":952,
                 "y":152
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":808,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"castlewalls1",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":680,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":809,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":680,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":810,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":976,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":817,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":648,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":818,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":672,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":819,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "colorVariant":"7",
                     "front":"ledgebrick"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "colorVariant":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":32,
                 "x":648,
                 "y":152
                }, 
                {
                 "height":40,
                 "id":821,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedscrappanel",
                     "colorVariant":"6"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "colorVariant":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":16,
                 "x":656,
                 "y":160
                }],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#ff0000",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"objects",
         "objects":[
                {
                 "gid":5900,
                 "height":40,
                 "id":790,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":48,
                 "x":336,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":5900,
                 "height":40,
                 "id":811,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":48,
                 "x":944,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":5900,
                 "height":40,
                 "id":820,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":48,
                 "x":640,
                 "y":200
                }],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#ffff00",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"wiring - lights & guns",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#ff0000",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"monsters & npcs",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#00ffff",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"wiring - locked door",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"outside the map",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"anchors etc",
         "objects":[
                {
                 "gid":244,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":753,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":512,
                 "y":16
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":245,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":756,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":72,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":246,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":804,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":984,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":245,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":813,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":944,
                 "y":200
                }],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"items",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }],
 "nextobjectid":822,
 "orientation":"orthogonal",
 "renderorder":"right-down",
 "tiledversion":"1.0.2",
 "tileheight":8,
 "tilesets":[
        {
         "firstgid":1,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/materials.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":196,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/supports.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":232,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/miscellaneous.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":254,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/liquids.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":282,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/ancient.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":444,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/apex.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":815,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/avian.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":1120,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/floran.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":1315,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/generic.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3241,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/glitch.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3467,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/human.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3751,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/hylotl.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3983,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/novakid.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":4046,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/breakable.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":4354,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/decorative.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":5773,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/door.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":5901,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/farmable.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":5976,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/furniture.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6322,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/light.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6764,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/railpoint.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6769,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/teleporter.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6809,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/trap.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7013,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/wire.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7231,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-type\/container.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7513,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-type\/teleporter.json"
        }],
 "tilewidth":8,
 "type":"map",
 "version":1,
 "width":204
}